Nada Alabed



+966 53 151 7402



Ndsaber1418@gmail.com



Riyadh, Saudi Arabia

Certifications and Courses

Course in cybersecurity and information crimes Qualifying in the introduction to cybersecurity Ministry Of communications and information Technology.

Ministry Of communications and information Technology - 2019

Course in CCNA (Routing and switching & introduction to Network)

Technical college In Riyadh - 2017

Microsoft official course in Active directory Services With windows Server

by Microsoft - 2021

Skills

- Troubleshooting
- Comfortable working in a team
- · Ability to work quickly under pressure
- · Interacting with Computers
- · Communication Skills
- Collecting Data and Information
- Problem-Solving And Decision-Making
- Communication
- Consulting and advising others
- · AD users and computers
- Basic knowledge on ERP Microsoft dynamics AX
- · Replace parts as required

Languages

- Arabic
- English

Summary

I hope to join a dynamic and self-esteem organization with potential for future growth, and contribution of new ideas. Desire challenging position in the filed of computer that utilities my technical and professional experience and knowledge.

Work Experience

Junior, IT Helpdesk

Al-ayuni investment and contracting CO.

2021- Present

- · Monitor and respond quickly to incoming requests relate to IT issues.
- Maintain computer systems and act as support if any system goes
 down
- Responsible for PC's, Printers, Servers and related equipment (monitor, keyboard, mouse, hard drive, etc).
- Maintain user PCs, including upgrades and configuration as needed.
- · Assist with onboarding of new users.
- Keep inventory of all equipment, software, and license users.
- · Install, configure, and upgrade PC software.
- Direct unresolved issues to the next level of support personnel.
- Installing or changing software to fix issues.
- Remotely accessing hardware or software for clients to make changes and fix problems.

Technical Support Specialist Saudibell Group CO.

2020 - 2021

- Install, modifie, and make minor repairs to computer hardware and software systems.
- Solve tickets using ServiceDesk Plus that represents requests or technical issues created by employees and explore and fix technical and process problems to maintain productivity.
- Consult with users to determine appropriate hardware and software needs and assists in placing orders.
- Gathering data to identify and evaluate technical purchasing options.
- Install software and necessary applications for workflow.
- Train users on new software in person or through a variety of tutorial channels, including self-guided training videos, user manuals, and digital instruction pages.

Technical Support Officer

Rowad Al-omaraa Co. For Education & Training

2019 - 2020

- keep computer systems running smoothly and ensure users get the maximum benefit from them
- install and configure computer hardware operating systems and applications
- · monitor and maintain computer systems and networks
- talk staff or clients through a series of actions, either face-to-face or over the phone, to help set up systems or resolve issues
- troubleshoot system and network problems, diagnosing and solving hardware or software faults

Education & Coope Training

Diploma in Computer Technical Support.

Technical College in Riyadh 2017-2018

Coope Training - Technical Support Unite.

Computer and information Department King Saud University 2018